Good morning, tunes. Is everyone ready
for the annual beach trip this year?
>> That's what I like to hear, friends.
This morning, we'll be going over
preparations. The bus will be pulling up
in front of Sprout's house at 10:00 this
morning. So, make sure you have all the
things you need. Remember to pee and
poop before getting on the bus, cuz
we're not going to be making any stops.
But if any of you find that you do have
to pee or poop while we're on the bus,
you can freely do it in my mouth. Aha,
that was a joke. I'm kidding. I don't
really want anyone to do that unless
they like you know really want to then
maybe.
>> Okay. Well, okay, Louie. Um, okay. Does
anyone have any questions? Goob,
>> where are we going?
>> The beach. What do you want, Shrimpo?
The beach is gay.
>> Dial, you need to turn your microphone
on.
It's still not on. Dial. Dial's just an
old man. It's fine. You guys give him
time. Screw it on. I'm calling him.
Dial. Dial. Pick up the phone. Press the
green button.
No. No. You see the button that looks
like a microphone? Click that one. You
might need to go to your settings. The
settings is the button that looks like
the gear. Yeah. Yeah. Make sure your
microphone is synced up. Oh my god.
Dial.
>> No tune is being forced to go. Shrimpo.
If you don't want to go, simply don't
step on the bus.
>> You are gay.
>> I failed to see how my sexuality has
anything to do with what we are
discussing this morning.
>> You have another question, Goop.
>> Can we be naked at the beach?
>> You're always naked, Goob.
>> Can we be even more naked? Like, can my
balls be uh swinging?
Hold on. Who keeps farting with their
camera off?
>> Me. I'm not farting.
>> Yana, please turn your camera on when
we're having a town meeting.
>> Are you on the toilet? How can you tell?
>> Cuz we can hear it.
>> Listen, baby girl.
>> Only Cosmo is allowed to call me that.
>> Baby girl, and this goes out to all 15
of you cabonas. I am not going to sit
here on the toilet and be humiliated by
all of you over what is a normal bodily
function. You are all on my time, not
the other way around. And don't you
forget that. Don't piss me off.
>> I'm blocking her.
>> Not if I block you first. Gringo.
>> She blocked me. Oh, I can already see
it. Everyone having fun at the beach.
All thanks to Danakus Dancifer. You're
all welcome. By the way, you aren't
going. You said you were coming over to
my house to help me finish my treehouse.
Remember? So, I planned this entire trip
for something I'm not even involved in.
I'm even paying the bus fee.
>> GG. Is everyone gone on the beach trip
yet? My burglar costume from Walmart
came in. When are we going around the
neighborhood to steal [__]
>> Damn it, Razle and Dazzle. I told you to
come later.
>> I wish you could come with us, but I
know how much the treehouse means to you
for some reason. You'll just have to
have enough fun for the both of us,
Cosmo. I don't know how I could do that
without my best friend, but I'll try.
I'm putting the donuts up here for
later. Uh, did I ask? Why are you so
mean to me all the time? Cuz you're mean
to me, too. All this arguing is making
me hungry. Old Andus could use a donut.
Get out of my walking path.
You placed them too high for me. I put
them really high up as a form of power
control. How does that make you feel?
Fat and short, obviously. Then what I
did worked. Give me the handsaw so I can
start cutting open the door. Oh,
how are we supposed to get back down
there with the walls nailed up? You
mentally challenged weed. We're stuck in
here and now we're going to die of
thirst. No, we ain't. We got donuts.
There's no water in donuts dip [__] If
a tune goes 3 days without water,
they're dead. Everybody knows that.
Probably 2 days in this blazing hot
heat. Don't talk like you know me.
You're going to die without it since
you're a strawberry. I don't need to eat
or drink to survive because I feed off
the heaven's light. That's called
photosynthesis. It has nothing to do
with God, you dweeb. Flowers get
nutrients from the sun, which is the
same thing that's kicking my ass. As an
actual strawberry that's been picked, I
don't got photosynthesis privileges
anymore. I can't be in the sun for 20
minutes or else I will die. It's so over
for me. Help. We need help. What the
hell do you think you're doing? You said
you're going to die in 20 minutes. Yeah,
but I can't have you calling for help on
my behalf. That is a sign of weakness on
my part.
Dandy, I'm afraid if we're going to get
through this, we're going to have to
drink each other's piss.
[__] we don't even got Wi-Fi up here.
Cosmo can't send me any sexy photos of
his new string lace transparent bikini.
Damn, I would have kind of liked to see
those photos, too. I should have never
even offered to build this godamn
treehouse for him. Wait, you're building
this whole entire treehouse just for
Cosmo? He's my best friend. I want to
give him whatever he wants. And when I
expressed the idea of building him one,
he was just so happy. You know,
you know, Cosmo, this weekend is going
to be our best friend overiversary. What
do you say I get you a gift? I was
thinking a treehouse. What the would I
do with a treehouse? I can't bake in one
of those things. That sounds like a fire
hazard. Ah, I'm joking, Cosmo. I'm not
actually going to hit you. Ah, now you
know I'm unpredictable, [__]
Astro, can I keep you company over here
while I eat my sandwich?
>> I won't stop you, Cosmo, but wouldn't
you rather spend these rare moments of
free time with someone less boring?
>> Sprout didn't come and he's the only
tune that lets me be around him because
I smell like [__] So, I figured why not
join the other social outcast.
>> Social outcast? So, you know I'm over
here because
>> because you're a freak of nature, right?
cause of your stupid forearms.
>> Yeah.
>> Do you want half of my sandwich?
>> I'd like that very much.
>> Let it go.
>> Don't you ever get lonely being all by
yourself.
>> I'm fine watching things play out from
afar usually.
What's wrong, potato chip? I guess I
can't text Sprout while we're at the
beach, can I? No Wi-Fi.
>> Some alone time is good from time to
time, Cosmo. You don't always need to be
Sprout's trophy wife.
>> You only saying that cuz ain't nobody
want to wife you up, loner ass [__]
>> What's Dy staring over here for?
>> He was staring at you from the back of
the bus, too, for some reason. Did you
do something to make him mad?
>> It's making me uncomfy.
>> Hey, Dial, go away. Your staring is why
everybody hates you.
Come on, let's go swimming.
>> But my arms.
>> It's fine. Nobody is going to make fun
of you or anything. You are way more
normal looking than you think. Some
would even say sexy.
>> Maybe you were on to something, Cosmo.
This isn't so bad after all.
>> Put those things away. Absolutely
disgusting creature.
>> What the hell is wrong with you, Astro?
This is a public beach.
>> Just so we're all clear, I'm not close
to him. He's the one who wanted to hang
out with me.
>> Astro, you doing okay?
>> I'm pooping right now. Boxed in.
>> I don't mind. Don't let what other tunes
say about your body get to you. All
right. We're all built different, and
you being ugly as [__] is what makes you
who you are. They hate me because of my
arms, not because I'm ugly.
>> Tounes can hate you for multiple
reasons, even if they don't say it.
>> Okay, can you shut the door?
>> I'm not done yet. If any tune starts
picking on you, you come to me. All
right,
>> I'll keep that in mind.
>> Yeah, shake those balloons, [__]
>> I got this one scraps.
>> Sorry.
>> It's fine. I'm not hurt or anything.
>> I'll leave you to finish your poop.
Oh, yeah. And take this air freshener.
You'll need it. Poop boy.
>> You're just giving me this?
>> Why not? You just pooped. Real bad
[__] are always carrying around at
least six cans on themselves at any
time. I carry around nine because I poop
a lot. So, I don't mind giving you one
that's almost empty.
>> Oh, hi Dial. Can you shut the door? I
want to request something of you first.
>> Can it wait until after I'm done
pooping?
>> I'm afraid it's quite urgent. Come get
some frozen dairy and sugar and walk
with me.
>> I just need to wipe first.
>> You don't need to. It's going to be just
us. Come along. What do you want?
>> Can you get me a dreamsicle?
Look, Shrimpo, they've got a romantic
sunset beach discount going on. So what?
I ain't got no [__] You can get two
milkshakes for the price of one if you
bring a girl or, you know, a boy.
>> Ew, you know not to talk about gays
around me.
>> I'm just saying if we act like a couple,
then maybe you could get some free ice
cream. You don't have to be mad at me.
Well, maybe I could play that game, but
there has to be strict ground rules. No
eye contact, no touching, and absolutely
no other forms of physical intimacy.
Next. Oh crap, Tisha, it's a couple of
them queers. That's Garden View for you.
The town's really been going downhill
since Dial Times came out of the closet.
Now every tune thinks they got rights.
>> Wow, Shrimpo Finn, I didn't know you two
were dating.
>> What the hell would give you that idea?
>> Wait, Goob. You mean you wouldn't think
anything different of us for liking
boys?
>> Why would I? There's no harm in two boys
being in love. Scrap says love makes the
world go round. And two of the people I
love most being in love just makes this
all so much better. See, Tesa, that's
the way you think if you're born
mentally challenged.
>> I hear that Goob cannot even mentally
develop past the age of five. That's
really funny.
>> You can't be saying that to him. You're
going to hurt his feelings.
>> Um, yeah, I can. We can even physically
assault him like this.
>> Yeah, Homo. And don't think we aren't
aware that you and Shrimpo are only
trying to get a free discount. Everybody
knows Shrimpo is the most homophobic
tune in town. Are you just going to
stand here and let them make Goob cry?
Shrimpo, I'm sorry, Shrimpo. If you and
Finn aren't dating, that's fine, too. I
just want you two to be happy with
whatever is going on.
What are you waiting for, [__] Assert
dominance on Goob. Hit him. Do it. Beat
his ass. I bet a part of Goob will even
find it to be really hot. Dunes with
mental handicaps love being hit because
it's the only form of physical intimacy
they can get. Cause God knows nobody is
going to give that poor creature the
hugs he's yearning for.
Go away, Goob. Nobody likes your free
and forward thinking around here.
I'm going to go tell Scraps you hit me
and then you'll be sorry.
Why do you keep looking out at the ocean
dial? You seem lost in thought.
>> Would it be a bother if I confronted you
about this?
>> What are you doing with my phone?
>> The way you're texting Dandicus is
rather flirtatious. Am I correct in
assuming you and him are an item?
>> What? No, nothing like that.
>> No, as in you will never be or not yet.
>> Danny doesn't even like boys. I know.
Oh, he sees the hints I throw his way,
but they're never reciprocated.
>> He reciprocated mine once, you know.
Dandy gave me the best year of my life,
even if it was behind closed doors for
no one to see.
>> When did that happen?
>> It started 2 years ago. Our relationship
lasted a full 12 months because neither
of us were quitters and we wanted to see
at least a full year's worth through to
see if we could make it work. How did it
end? Dial.
>> Did you know the paint the use on trains
is specialized? It can last 20 to 30
years before a full repaint is needed.
Lighter colors are also used because
they help the trains stay cooler in
direct sunlight. That's why most trains
you see are white, red, or yellow.
>> Jesus Christ, Dial. I can't keep doing
this. I'm breaking up with you.
>> Oh, was it something I said?
>> All you talk about is trains. Well, I'm
sorry that it's my current
hyperfixation, dear.
>> A hyperfixation that lasts a full year,
though. You're the one who made me
realize I'm not gay. Dial. Cuz if all
gay people do is talk about trains, then
I seriously cannot be one of you.
>> Hey, Astro, how them balls hanging?
>> I was just going to McDonald's to buy a
hash brown. Do you want to come share
one with me?
>> Only if you don't give me a fun fact
about trains. Haha. I got to tell you
about this one [__] I've been seeing
lately.
>> I never talk about trains dandy. I'm not
that autistic.
>> Well, this dumb [__] wouldn't shut up
about them. I guess the few times I
slapped her around wasn't good enough to
set her straight, so I dumped her sorry
ass this morning. Hey, buy me a
hamburger and fries when we get to
McDonald's.
>> I'll see what I can do.
>> See, this is what I like about you,
Astro. You just do as I say like a good
[__]
>> You should stop trying to chase after
him before you get hurt. You don't have
to worry about me, Dial. I'm a tough
tune. If a day ever came where I
confessed my feelings to Dandy and he
turned me down, my heart could take it.
>> I don't mean your heart, Astro. There
are other tunes after Dandy's heart
who'd swiftly beat your ass if you were
standing in their way.
>> Is that a thinly veiled threat dial?
>> All I'm saying, Astro is
a Glock 19. Where in the hell were you
hiding that thing?
>> You can hide a lot of things in your ass
when people are only looking at you from
the front.
>> Astro, this is madness. You've got to
I'm alive. My tune ability lets me take
a moment I previously just lived and
turn it into a dream, erasing it
completely as if it never occurred, like
it was just a fart in the wind.
Think of what just happened as a future
that could come if you bring this up
again. Pick your battles wisely going
forward, [__] Thanks for the dreams,
sickle, but I have got to go wipe my ass
now.
A gee, Sprout, you ain't looking too
hot.
I told you I need consistent fluid
intake. I haven't had any water in 10
minutes, which means in another 10
minutes I will die.
Well, [__] happens, I suppose. Who could
have seen this coming? I'll be sure to
keep your memory alive by, you know,
baking. What else do you do? Or is that
it? It's getting hard for me to speak
about goddamn time. Your voice has
always been annoying. Hey, what do you
say I sit next to you in your final
moments, pal? That would be pretty
bitching, I suppose.
I'm going to make sure there's like a 2
ft distance between us cuz any closer
would be gay. The two of us had a hell
of a ride, haven't we, Dancifer? We sure
did, Seedley. We sure did. I need you to
pee in my mouth, Dandy. Please. You've
got to water me.
Hold up. Roll that back. Please nourish
me, Dandy. Nobody else has to know. If I
don't swallow your premium quality
golden iker to quench my thirst, I'm
going to die.
>> Yeah, yeah, I get it. You don't have to
beg for it, big dog. Open up wide
twinkle toes. It's coming in hot right
from the faucet.
Please, nerd, give me your sweet nectar,
>> I'm inside. What do I do now? Gigi,
>> huh? Do what I TOLD YOU, TOODLES. UNLOCK
THE DOOR.
>> It's too high for me.
>> [__] I will kill you. Don't think you
being only 8 years old will stop me. If
you want to be on this team, you're
going to have to learn to compromise.
>> I will go find something that I can
stand on then to reach the lock.
>> That's good. Mentally challenged baby.
Move your ass.
>> Are you sure Sprout isn't home? We can't
spend another year in jail.
>> I'm telling you, Fruitcakes, all of
Garden View is out on their beach
vacation. Today's going to be the heist
of the lifetime and [__] Why can't I
just phase through the door? Won't that
be faster than whatever Toodles is
doing?
>> Connie, shut up.
>> I found a stool under the kitchen sink.
>> Do it faster next time.
>> Sprout. Hey, Sprout. Come look at this.
Razle and Dazzle are in your house. Hey,
Razle. Dazzle, what the hell are you
doing?
>> I said to stay away from the windows,
you two.
>> No, you said Sprout and Dandy weren't
even supposed to be here. Well,
improvise something.
>> Uh, you left your door unlocked, Sprout.
So, we're having to look around to make
sure nobody broke in.
>> Oh, thanks for being a real one. Very
cool.
Hey, what is Toodles doing over there?
The eightball baby is stealing all the
engraved silverware I got Cosmo for
Christmas. That gift sounds kind of gay.
Thieves. Thieves.
>> Nobody move in the name of all that is
righteous. It's the Halloween event
tunes.
>> Sylvester, this isn't what it looks
like.
>> Dear sister, I always knew you were a
[__] It does not surprise me one bit
that we would end up on opposite sides
of society. Sexy pumpkin baby, I choose
you. Claim your victim and charge. Show
no fear,
>> Rebecca. I always knew the greatest
battle in all of Garden View would come
down to the two tunes with the fattest
asses. Yeah, you have no idea how long
I've been waiting to beat your face in.
Bring it, undead, [__]
None of my blows are landing, you guys.
They're just phasing through this [__]
It takes a ghost to beat a ghost.
>> Really, potato chip? You just hit your
own sister.
>> I lost my mortal form in the 1600s,
where it was not only freely allowed to
hit women, but even encouraged. The
amount of blood we once shared in our
veins mean not when those veins exist no
longer since we're ghosts and [__]
Sylvester. Connie is getting away.
>> Coward. A coward is what you are and
what you will always be.
>> She's trying to steal my phone.
>> Oh my god. What the hell? Oh my god.
>> Everybody, something's going down at
Garden View. We need to go home right
away.
So, you thought you could just steal our
[__] while we were away?
What will become of us now?
We are all gathered here today in this
bombass treehouse that Sprout and I
built with the power of friendship to
pay our respects and remember these
tunes. Not as criminals who tried to
steal our [__] while everyone was out of
town. But as our friends, would anybody
like to say any last words about these
crazy [__] before they are put to rest?
Hey Lou, would it be cool if I sat next
to you? I'd love for you to sit next to
me, Dandy.
>> Thanks, Lou. You're very handsome.
>> Well, haha. Uh, couldn't even tell you
why I just did that.
>> I'm sorry about your sister, Sylvester.
Are you going to go up there and say
something out of respect for her?
>> I should, shouldn't I? Alas, I do not
give a single [__] for she caused her
own death this day by walking the path
of thievery.
>> Then, do you want to make like pee and
piss off back to my place? My parents
are still missing, so I'm living all
alone. So, nothing's stopping us from
doing whatever you want. I can help you
forget all about your sister and [__]
>> You little te's?
>> I'm going to miss these tunes. They were
like my very best friends.
>> [__] you didn't even know any of them.
See, Sprout, this is why I hate Poppy.
Even at a funeral, she's always got to
be the center of attention.
>> You don't know that. Maybe they were
closer than we thought.
>> Poppy who died today.
See, she doesn't even know.
>> Are you done?
>> I mean, I guess.
>> Then be gone with you and your fake
bubble titties. When Toodles first
showed up to Garden View, I thought,
"Wow, what an ugly baby." But even so, I
was often chosen as Toodles's caretaker
because nobody in town liked her. I'm
going to miss taking care of her. But
more importantly, I'm going to miss the
weekly $20 Dandy gave me for child care
because oh boy, that was a lot of money.
I was able to get Uber Eats twice a week
with that money if I ordered from not
too far from my house and didn't tip. I
get the money was supposed to go to
Toodles probably, but I didn't really
care. And to be honest, I don't think
Dandy cared either.
>> Love you, Roger. Never forget that. I
will miss that little eightball creature
with my whole heart. And and it should
have been me. Damn it. Damn you, God.
She was just an ugly baby.
I've got to be honest. I didn't know a
ghost could die by a gun. This is news
to me as I am sure it is to you all as
well. Do not mourn my sister's passing,
for it was simply her time. Instead,
mourn me, for I will now have to live
with the boredom of knowing that I, too,
could die by being shot by a Glock 19.
Would somebody like to come up here and
say something nice about Razle and
Dazzle? Or are we going to act like that
two-headed freak of nature doesn't
exist? Like how nobody who plays Dandy's
World buys them because 2,000 IICore
costs way too much for what they provide
gameplaywise.
No, I think we are done here. Over there
in the corner, you will find a plate of
cookies and fresh orange juice made from
oranges I squeezed from my very own
orange tree.
>> Hey Lou, where's Astro? I know either
Razzle or Dazzle Astro $6, so I'm sure
he's taking it harder than a dick in the
ass.
>> He didn't take the bus back with us.
>> But the beach is 67 mi away. How is he
supposed to get back home?
The others told me you didn't come home,
so I asked Gliston if I could borrow his
electric scooter. It goes about 12 mph,
so I was about to get here in like 10
minutes.
>> Is everything fine
>> now that you're here? I just like the
view and didn't want to leave. The way
the night sky is reflecting off the
water. Doesn't it look like our own
little sea of stars here on Earth?
>> Not really. You wouldn't believe what
went down at Sprout's house while you
all were having a blast here. Gigi died
and Connie and Razzle and Dazzle and
Toodles.
>> Dandy, are you in love with Dial?
>> What are you trying to say?
>> A long time ago, you told me there was
this girl you dumped cuz she was
mentally challenged as [__] Was that
girl actually
astro? You know I'm as straight as a
pencil. Everyone's going to be spreading
lies that they shared a bed with me cuz
I'm just that [__] Don't believe
whatever anyone told you about my past.
Have I ever lied to you, potato chip?
What are best friends for if not to
share the honest to goodness truth?
>> Yeah, I believe you.
>> If there is something about me you still
don't know, that doesn't make it a
secret. It just means I haven't talked
about it yet. Best friends don't have to
tell each other everything right away.
You know,
you'll know everything there is to know
about me if you are alive long enough.
If you happen to die before knowing
stupid stuff like the annoying [__]
I've dated before, well, that's not my
problem. I know it's not the end of the
month yet, but stop by my house before
midnight so I can extract some of that
acre anyway. I'm not giving you a choice
this time.
Oh, hey. Did you like today's episode of
Dandy's World? If you thought it was
bitching, why not support Tamers 12345
by joining Patreon? If you do within the
next 20 minutes, I won't punch Astro.
For just a $3 subscription, you can let
Tamers know you want to see more Dandy's
World stuff. You also get access to
wallpapers and a lot of gifts that were
used in this episode, as well as gifts
from all the previous episodes. Say
something before they're gone, Astro.
>> Oh, um, hi, my name is Astro. I like
creamed corn and hot milk with cinnamon.
>> That's our astral. All right. He
certainly likes creamed corn. And what
did you say?
>> I don't remember. My mind's all hazy
because uh the extraction.
>> He means extraction. Haha. See you next
time, [__]
>> Go away. Nobody
down.
I won't drag on down ruin way
I won't drag on down the ruin down
the way. I won't drag on down the ruin
way
down.
I won't drag on down
the way.
I won't drag on down the ruin way
down.
I won't drag on down
the way. I won't drag on down
way
down.
I won't drag on down
the Hey.